Hey, I'm at the Obscene Trite Fair again.
It's my third time this year and I'm going to have a look around and see what designers I don't know yet and what stands.
But I also know where I'm going to rest my feet tonight if I can walk anymore.
Right here!
When I realized
I told you I'm wondering what it's like
Colleen, show me your design
Show me the power of light
I'm here at the Swedish Color booth.
They're from Sweden.
They're here in Karlsruhe which is really cool and they have one new thing.
They have anklets, ankle calves.
They're brand new, and this is the first time
I'm seeing them too.
Thanks to my wonderful model for showing them.
I'm going to try on this latex ensemble now and I think it's pretty cute, skirt and a
jacket.
I will show you some specialties when I wear it.
I'm checking in the mirror here,
because I think it's adorable.
It's so cute with the paitland part and the jacket.
And it's blue, so of course I like it.
Makes, yeah, feminine hips.
And the biker style of the jacket is really awesome.
I like the cut.
But I have to show you some details,
because this is stitched latex.
So it's completely made out of latex,
and also glued, but also stitched.
I just love to
like pimp up every catsuit with a corset waist ginger this one is latex again because latex
fashion design the name of the company is what they do and i love the combination here because
we have a bit of blue inside here which of course matches with my hair so it's fun
i just met fellow youtuber and out scene influencer mary ellen hey hi nice to meet you nice
Nice to meet you too. Tell me a few sentences. What can people see on your channel on YouTube?
I do BDSM education and lifestyle fashion.
And so we're at the Opscene today and we came up with a little fun idea.
We're each gonna pick a challenge and outfit for each other.
Okay, so let's head over to the fairs, booths, fair boots, whatever.
And see if we can find outfits for each other.
That's gonna be fun.
I'm waiting for Mary to come out again because she's trying on a catsuit.
Here at the Benno von Stein booth.
I talked to her a bit and yeah, I think we'll pick it up for some accessories.
Ooh!
Nice!
I really like it! How do you feel? I thought it's the first time you're wearing a catsuit!
Yeah, it's really tight, but I really like it!
Nice!
What do you think?
I think it looks awesome! I have the same catsuit in like four letters, so I know this cut is so cool,
but we're going to pimp it up with some accessories, some glitter!
I love how it's in just a waist.
Yes.
Far heels and black.
It's an epic win I'd say.
Okay.
I think you definitely picked the right outfit.
Haha.
My plan for this challenge was to take her to a designer I know very well and I know
what he can do and that his cuts are superior, Benno von Stein.
You can see a lot of other Benno von Stein videos on my channel, check them out.
And I think it worked pretty well, she looks awesome in the catsuit.
So I have an outfit I have to try on now.
You picked something.
I picked something.
I hope you like it.
I'm ready!
Oooh!
Wow!
The material of the smirk!
Holding the microphone in my hands
because it's too delicate to clip onto.
How do you feel?
I feel very elegant
because it's so light and see-through.
It has bunny ears.
Bunny ears, correct.
Oh, interesting.
I have bunny ears.
It has very fancy lashes.
Oh.
Oh, wow.
The skirt is amazing.
But most importantly, what do you think?
I have to think I will look in the mirror first
so I think I prefer this one I prefer your catsuit and my cloak they were
really nice outfits also nice contrast so really something different yes
challenge accomplished yeah done thank you for joining on my channel
thank you check her out I will tag the channel down below and link everything
of course. Let's have another look around.
A forest filled with fear of the wind Like the moon so beautiful from afar
But shattered on the surface of the skies A sea with no more fish
Planets without air Whales with no more song
And now I'm gonna die with the wind
I had a wonderful day here at the Obscene in Karlsruhe today and now dinner because
I'm hungry it's half past nine already I'm starving but I met so many great people and
I hope you enjoyed this video check out the videos from the last years and also all the
other videos on my channel leave me some thumbs up and subscribe see you around bye